

# Sundhar Karunanidi



Flat 3 Tan House, 3 Clayton Street Bristol,

Easton,

England





SundharDevKarunanidi@gmail.com



### **About Me**

I am a Web Developer with lots of experience in C#, ASP.Net (Framework and Core), JavaScript, CSS3 and HTML5. The majority of work I have done has been for large scale enterprises CI/CD projects for clients such as Greene King and Electrolux, I have also worked in TDD/BDD projects. As part of this I have worked with CMS's such as Umbraco and EpiServer, oftentimes being tasked with maintaining, extending or fixing issues related to them. Recently I have been involved with the Node.js initiative as a mentee to further Node.js. I am keen to learn and a diligent worker. More recently I have been working with Azure and AWS.

# Primary Technologies:

C#
ASP.Net Core
NUnit
Umbraco
SourceTree
MSSQL Server
Razor
CSS3
HTML5
Azure Suite
MongoDB

# Technologies I have delivered with...

Confluence
Jira
BitBucket
Notion
Episerver
React
Vue
Miro (Design work)

## **EXPERIENCE**

Jun 2021 - Current Backend Engineer/Full Stack • Felinesoft • Bristol, UK

#### What I worked on:

- Working in a smaller sprint team with more responsibility with autonomy, whilst working closer with the client and their team.
- Large migration project of legacy code in an older version of Umbraco (7) to (8) whilst keeping the legacy code running simultaneously to the newer version. (using reverse proxies and multiple rewrite rules)
- Delivered multiple extensions alongside migrations. These included complex assessment tools and event booking systems (CRM integrated).
- Working with a CRM and implementing data from it into our code using an API.
- Delivered with Azure products such as table storage, blob storage, SQL storage, ADb2c, AppInsights. Also setting up and managing resources within Azure.
- Managing releases via Git.
- Delivered training to newer developers whilst mentoring them.

### Nov 2019 - Jun 2021

Web Developer/Full Stack/Programmer • Zone Digital • Bristol, UK

#### Certifications:

- 98-375: MTA: HTML5 Application Development Fundamentals
- BCS Level 4 Diploma in Software Development Methodologies

#### What I worked on:

- Created a Configuration Viewer Tool in EpiServer for Electrolux to allow editors to see configurations for all brands and markets, using C# ASP.Net.
- Maintaining Microservices, such as Events Portal and Book a Table at enterprise level for Greene King using React JavaScript library.
- Improving core web vitals through implementing lazy loading site wide.
- Working in a CI pipeline and learning how to deliver using the CD pipeline
- Removing legacy code and previous services from solution and CMS to clear Umbraco Error Logs.
- Extending websites using the Episerver and Umbraco CMS platforms.
- Participating in an Agile multidisciplinary team to contribute to stand ups, refinements, retrospectives, planning, example mapping (Gherkin and BDD) and demos to clients.
- Developing and extending front-end website functionality using JavaScript, HTML5, React and CSS3
- Using Confluence to update documentation and use JIRA to manage workflow efficiently.
- Experience using DataDog log management and APM.

#### Side Projects:

 Created an online CRUD application for team members to create and track training requests. Achieved using ASP.Net MVC (C#), Identity Framework and Razor. I also created a relational database and entity relationship diagrams.

Jan 2017 - Nov 2019

WordPress Web Development • Self Employed • Bristol, UK

#### What I worked on:

- Designing and building WordPress websites using Elementor.
- Giving local small scale businesses an online presence.
- Build simple CSS and HTML blocks.
- Teach clients how to maintain and improve their own websites using a CMS.

# **EDUCATION**

University of Bristol – Aerospace Engineering (HND) – Bristol, UK

## Transferable skills:

- Design and Computing (C Programming Basics and CAD design work)
  Engineering Mathematics 1 & 2 (Statistical Modeling and Algebraic Concepts)

<sup>\*</sup>Please have a look at my GitHub pages website.